Tyler Vance

Software Engineer

♥ Hiram, GA trvance.github.io

in LinkedIn

Profile

Hello. Just your typical, determined software engineer looking to continue to grow. Creative, teamfocused and friendly. 3 years of experience with Javascript, CSS, HTML, React and more. Currently helping entertainment company start an in-house software department. Skilled in agile processes, full-stack development, git, and working with databases.

Education

2017 - 2021 **Computer Science** Valdosta Valdosta State University

Professional Experience

2021 - present **Software Engineer**

Atlanta Rigging Systems 🗷 Atlanta, GA

Worked with the Mechanical Engineers and their PLC programs to create modern and user friendly front end applications to create a much simpler interface for the rigging crew to interact with, when setting up, testing, and

running entertainment shows.

2019 - 2021 **Shift Leader**

Valdosta, GA Surcheros Fresh Mex

Managing, customer service, stress handling in extreme situations and time

management. The basics.

Work Projects

Curtain Sniffer

Atlanta Rigging Systems

ReactJS front end application wrapped in Electron was used to produce a clean, simple interface to control speed, length of curtain, duration etc. of a curtain sniffer module.

Load Cells

Atlanta Rigging Systems

A Visual Basic program for the rigging crew to upload a plot rig and connect to chain hoist motors to allow them to place them on the rig plot to quickly see the motors locations and weights. Was later converted to ReactJS (wrapped in Electron) and nodeOPCUA on the backend to connect to the motors.